http://gamefreaks365.com/privacy-policy

NEWSREVIEWSABOUT USNEWSLETTER#gamefreaks365NEWSREVIEWSABOUT USNEWSLETTERTwitterFacebookYouTubeEditorialsEsportsIndie GamesInterviewsMobileNerd CulturePCRetro GamingTabletopVR NintendoSwitchSonyPlayStation 4PlayStation 5MicrosoftXbox OneXbox Series XSearch GameFreaks365
Last updated: January 29, 2019 Game Freaks 365 (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates http://gamefreaks365.com (“the site” or “the website”). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information we receive from users of the site. By using the site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. What personal data we collect and why we collect itCommentsWhen visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.MediaIf you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.CookiesIf you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.Embedded content from other websitesArticles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.AnalyticsLike many websites, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our site, known as log data.Log data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, and other statistics.In addition, we may use third-party services, such as Google Analytics, that collect, monitor and analyze this data.Who we share your data withThe only data that is shared with third-party companies is for internal analytics (i.e. Google Analytics), spam prevention (i.e. Akismet), and social media likes and sharing. We may provide anonymized analytics to potential advertisers, but we will never include personal information.How long we retain your dataIf you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.What rights you have over your dataIf you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to remove it. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.Where we send your dataVisitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.Changes to our Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy is effective as of January 29, 2019. It will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time, and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of our website after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.SIf we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by placing a prominent notice on our website.Contact UsIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.Most Read Kyle
|
December 1, 2020Rainbow Six Siege is out now on PS5 and Xbox Series X Deals
|
December 2, 2020Humble RPG Book Bundle: Warhammer 40K: Black Crusade & Only War out now Dexter
|
December 3, 20208-year-old gamer joins esports team, receives $33K signing bonusReviews Andrew McKissock
|
November 29, 2020Godfall Review Drew
|
November 28, 2020Yakuza: Like a Dragon Review Andrew McKissock
|
November 22, 2020Call of Duty: Black Ops Cold War ReviewRetro Gaming Samantha
|
December 7, 2020Scott Pilgrim vs. The World: The Game Complete Edition release date announced Samantha
|
November 30, 2020Saga Frontier Remastered announced Kyle
|
November 26, 2020Can’t find Game & Watch: Super Mario Bros? Here are some Black Friday optionsIndie Games Kyle
|
December 10, 2020Heaven’s Vault release date confirmed for Nintendo Switch Kyle
|
December 9, 2020Vigor launches on PS4 and PS5 Kyle
|
December 9, 2020Grow Big (or Go Home) is an indoor gardening simulator LinksGame Deals 365Game Trailers 365Video Game Streamers© 2020 GameFreaks365Designed by Angel Cortés | Privacy Policy | OpenCritic
